let bible_question = [
    {
        question:"For God so loved the world that he gave his one and only Son, that whoever believes in him shall not perish but have eternal life.",
        choices:{
            a:"John 3:16",
            b:"2 Corinthians 5:7",
            c:"Matthew 21:22"
        },
        answer:'John 3:16'
    },
    {
        question:"Therefore he is able to save completely those who come to God through him, because he always lives to intercede for them.",
        choices:{
            a:"John 3:16",
            b:"Hebrews 7:25",
            c:"Romans 10:9"
        },
        answer:'Hebrews 7:25'
    },
    {
        question:"but in your hearts honor Christ the Lord as holy, always being prepared to make a defense to anyone who asks you for a reason for the hope that is in you; yet do it with gentleness and respect",
        choices:{
            a:"John 3:16",
            b:"Hebrews 7:25",
            c:"Peter 3:15"
        },
        answer:'Peter 3:15'
    },
    {
        question:"Unless you believe that I am who I claim to be, you will die in your sins.",
        choices:{
            a:"John 7:38",
            b:"2 Corinthians 5:7",
            c:"John 8:24"
        },
        answer:'John 8:24'
    },
    {
        question:"Whoever believes in me, as Scripture has said, rivers of living water will flow from within them.",
        choices:{
            a:"John 3:16",
            b:"John 7:38",
            c:"Luke 1:37"
        },
        answer:'John 7:38'
    },
    {
        question:"So faith comes from hearing, and hearing through the word of Christ.",
        choices:{
            a:"Mark 5:36",
            b:"Romans 10:17",
            c:"Luke 1:37"
        },
        answer:'Romans 10:17'
    },
    {
        question:"Overhearing what they said, Jesus told him, “Don’t be afraid; just believe.",
        choices:{
            a:"Mark 5:36",
            b:"Romans 10:17",
            c:"Psalm 31:3"
        },
        answer:'Mark 5:36'
    },
    {
        question:"Who is it that overcomes the world? Only the one who believes that Jesus is the Son of God.",
        choices:{
            a:"Luke 1:37",
            b:"1 John 5:5",
            c:"Psalm 31:3"
        },
        answer:'1 John 5:5'
    },
    {
        question:"If you declare with your mouth, “Jesus is Lord,” and believe in your heart that God raised him from the dead, you will be saved.",
        choices:{
            a:"Luke 1:37",
            b:"1 John 5:5",
            c:"Romans 10:9"
        },
        answer:'Romans 10:9'
    },
    {
        question:"For we walk by faith, not by sight.",
        choices:{
            a:"1 John 5:5",
            b:"2 Corinthians 5:7",
            c:"Mark 5:36"
        },
        answer:'2 Corinthians 5:7'
    },
    {
        question:"That your faith might not rest in the wisdom of men but in the power of God.",
        choices:{
            a:"1 John 5:5",
            b:"2 Corinthians 5:7",
            c:"1 Corinthians 2:5"
        },
        answer:'1 Corinthians 2:5'
    },
    {
        question:"And whatever you ask in prayer, you will receive, if you have faith.",
        choices:{
            a:"Matthew 21:22",
            b:"2 Corinthians 5:7",
            c:"John 8:24"
        },
        answer:'Matthew 21:22'
    },
    {
        question:"For nothing will be impossible with God.",
        choices:{
            a:"Luke 1:37",
            b:"Romans 10:97",
            c:"John 8:24"
        },
        answer:'Luke 1:37'
    },
    {
        question:"Be on guard. Stand firm in the faith. Be courageous. Be strong.",
        choices:{
            a:"1 Corinthians 16:13",
            b:"Romans 10:97",
            c:"Matthew 21:22"
        },
        answer:'1 Corinthians 16:13'
    },
    {
        question:"I can do all things through him who strengthens me.",
        choices:{
            a:"1 John 5:5",
            b:"Philippians 4:13",
            c:"Luke 1:37"
        },
        answer:'Philippians 4:13'
    },
    {
        question:"In my distress I called to the LORD, and he answered me.",
        choices:{
            a:"Psalm 120:1",
            b:"1 Corinthians 2:5",
            c:"Luke 1:37"
        },
        answer:'Psalm 120:1'
    },
    {
        question:"Jesus looked at them and said, ‘With man it is impossible, but not with God. For all things are possible with God.",
        choices:{
            a:"Romans 10:9",
            b:"Mark 10:27",
            c:"Matthew 21:22"
        },
        answer:'Mark 10:27'
    },
    {
        question:"Do everything in love.",
        choices:{
            a:"1 Corinthians 16:14",
            b:"Mark 10:27",
            c:"Luke 1:37"
        },
        answer:'1 Corinthians 16:14'
    },
    {
        question:"As water reflects the face,so one’s life reflects the heart.",
        choices:{
            a:"Proverbs 27:19",
            b:"2 Corinthians 5:7",
            c:"Psalm 120:1"
        },
        answer:'Proverbs 27:19'
    },
    {
        question:"Since you are my rock and my fortress, for the sake of your name lead and guide me.",
        choices:{
            a:"Psalm 31:3",
            b:"2 Corinthians 5:7",
            c:"Matthew 5:14"
        },
        answer:'Psalm 31:3'
    },
]